<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Jay Tang</title>
    <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brian Jay Tang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bjaytang.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rearchitecting Classification Frameworks For Increased Robustness</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_001/</guid>
      <description>Authors Varun Chandrasekaran , Brian Tang, Nicolas Papernot , Kassem Fawaz , Somesh Jha , Xi Wu Abstract While generalizing well over natural inputs, neural networks are vulnerable to adversarial inputs. Existing defenses against adversarial inputs have largely been detached from the real world. These defenses also come at a cost to accuracy. Fortunately, there are invariances of an object that are its salient features; when we break them it will necessarily change the perception of the object.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Opting-Out Actually Opt Me Out</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_007/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_007/</guid>
      <description>Authors Duc Bui , Brian Tang, Kang G. Shin Conference Under review at 29th ACM Conference on Computer and Communications Security (2022)
Abstract Abstract will be shared after full paper acceptance.
Figures Relevant Links </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Detection of Consent Violations</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_005/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_005/</guid>
      <description>Authors Duc Bui , Brian Tang, Kang G. Shin Conference Under review at 32nd USENIX Security Symposium (2023)
Abstract Abstract will be shared after full paper acceptance.
Figures Relevant Links </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONFIDANT: A Privacy Controller for Social Robots</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_004/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_004/</guid>
      <description>Authors Brian Tang, Dakota Sullivan , Bengisu Cagiltay , Varun Chandrasekaran , Kassem Fawaz , Bilge Mutlu Conference 17th ACM/IEEE International Conference on Human-Robot Interaction (2022)
Abstract As social robots become increasingly prevalent in day-to-day environments, they will participate in conversations and appropriately manage the information shared with them. However, little is known about how robots might appropriately discern the sensitivity of information, which has major implications for human-robot trust. As a first step to address a part of this issue, we designed a privacy controller, CONFIDANT, for conversational social robots, capable of using contextual metadata (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fairness Properties of Face Recognition and Obfuscation Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_003/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_003/</guid>
      <description>Authors Harrison Rosenberg , Brian Tang, Kassem Fawaz , Somesh Jha Conference Under review at 32nd USENIX Security Symposium (2023)
Abstract The proliferation of automated face recognition in various commercial and government sectors has caused significant privacy concerns for individuals. A recent, popular approach to address these privacy concerns is to employ evasion attacks against the metric embedding networks powering face recognition systems. Face obfuscation systems generate imperceptible perturbations, when added to an image, cause the face recognition system to misidentify the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EyeShield: Real-Time Shoulder Surfing Protection for Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_008/</guid>
      <description>Authors Brian Tang, Kang G. Shin Conference Under review at 32nd USENIX Security Symposium (2023)
Abstract Abstract will be shared after full paper acceptance.
Figures Relevant Links </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inconsitency Detection in Browser Extension Privacy Practices</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_006/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_006/</guid>
      <description>Authors Duc Bui , Brian Tang, Kang G. Shin Conference Conditionally accepted at 43rd IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (2022)
Abstract Abstract will be shared after full paper acceptance.
Figures Relevant Links </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face-Off: Adversarial Face Obfuscation</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/projects/post_002/</guid>
      <description>Authors Varun Chandrasekaran , Chuhan Gao , Brian Tang, Kassem Fawaz , Somesh Jha , Suman Banerjee Conference 21st Symposium Privacy Enhancing Technologies (2021)
Abstract Advances in deep learning have made face recognition technologies pervasive. While useful to social media platforms and users, this technology carries significant privacy threats. Coupled with the abundant information they have about users, service providers can associate users with social interactions, visited places, activities, and preferences&amp;ndash;some of which the user may not want to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Biosketch I’m a 1st year Computer Science PhD student at the University of Michigan and a member of the Real-Time Computing Lab (advised by Prof. Kang Shin ). Currently, my research focuses on the intersection between usable privacy and machine learning. As an undergraduate student, I was a part of the Wisconsin Privacy and Security Group working with Prof. Kassem Fawaz , Prof. Varun Chandrasekaran , and Prof. Somesh Jha on machine learning security and privacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies and Traveling</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/funstuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/funstuff/</guid>
      <description>Hobbies Cooking Reading Investing Video games, tabletop games, board games Anime, manga Skateboarding, biking Meditation, taijiquan Traveling Domestic San Francisco, Los Angeles | California Seattle | Washington Chicago | Illinois Madison | Wisconsin Minneapolis | Minnesota St. Louis | Missouri Orlando | Florida San Antonio | Texas Portland | Maine Boston, Cambridge | Massachusetts Ann Arbor | Michigan Las Vegas | Nevada Springdale | Utah Washington, D.C. International Tokyo, Osaka, Kyoto, Nagano | Japan Cancun | Mexico Toronto | Canada Munich | Germany Salzburg, Hallstatt | Austria Paris, Tours | France Prague, Cesky Krumlov | Czech Republic Taipei | Taiwan The Bahamas Jamaica Parks &amp;rsquo;n Stuff Zion National Park Redwood National Park Sequoia National Park Yosemite National Park Golden Gate Park Monterey Bay Griffith Park Great Smoky Mountains National Park Hawaiʻi Volcanoes National Park Haleakalā National Park Mammoth Cave National Park Gateway Arch National Park Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore Shawnee National Forest Fort Williams Park </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers and PDFs</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/papers/</guid>
      <description>Overview Here, I host a list of all the papers I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved with as well as some of my course and research notes. Unfortunately, I can&amp;rsquo;t share papers undergoing revision/review. Some titles have been altered to ensure reviewers are unable to search for papers undergoing review. Finally I have some recommendations for papers that left a big impact on me and my research.
Publications/Papers CONFIDANT: A Privacy Controller for Social Robots Fairness Properties of Face Recognition and Obfuscation Systems Face-Off: Adversarial Face Obfuscation Rearchitecting Classification Frameworks For Increased Robustness Course Papers An Analysis and Proposed Design for Artificial General Intelligence A Standardized Model for Transparent Data Privacy DJGRAD: Sparse Gradients Protocol for Distributed Assisted Learning in CAVs Toxicity Detection and Mitigation on Social Networking Platforms Does IBP Scale?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Readings</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/reading/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;m Reading Sorry I&amp;rsquo;m Late, I Didn&amp;rsquo;t Want to Come The Black Swan Thinking, Fast and Slow Why We Sleep: Unlocking the Power of Sleep and Dreams The Road to Character Irrational Exuberance What Is Mathematics?: An Elementary Approach to Ideas and Methods The Brain That Changes Itself Bone Recommendations Mindfulness The Headspace Guide to Meditation &amp;amp; Mindfulness The Upward Spiral Workbook The Book of Joy The Four Agreements Mindset Privacy Industry Unbound Privacy as Contextual Integrity Communication Privacy Management Theory Computer Science Understanding Machine Learning: From Theory to Algorithms Cracking the Coding Interview Entrepreneurship The 4-Hour Workweek Zero to One The Ride of a Lifetime: Lessons Learned from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company Life Atomic Habits: Tiny Changes, Remarkable Results Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat Never Split the Difference: Negotiating as if Your Life Depended on It Persepolis: The Story of a Childhood Tuesdays with Morrie Born a Crime Brave New World For Fun The Hobbit Zima Blue The Martian What If?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/service/</guid>
      <description>External/Sub Reviewer PoPETS | Spring 2021 USENIX Security | Spring 2020 Mentoring I hope to mentor some students to be great researchers soon!
Volunteering Feed My Starving Children Westmont Public Library Burgess Square Healthcare &amp;amp; Rehab Centre Transcend UW Sakura-Con Other various small events and fundraisers </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/page/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d like to teach and TA with the extra time I&amp;rsquo;ll have after finishing my PhD course requirements. Along with teaching at the University of Michigan, I&amp;rsquo;d like to volunteer and teach Computer Science at K-12 schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ExtPrivA Paper Accepted</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_009/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_009/</guid>
      <description>Our paper, Detection of Inconsistencies in Privacy Practices of Browser Extensions , got accepted at IEEE S&amp;amp;P 2022!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HRI Paper Accepted</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_008/</guid>
      <description>Our paper, Confidant: A Privacy Controller for Social Robots , got accepted at HRI 2022!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD 1st Year Fellowship</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_007/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_007/</guid>
      <description>I received the University of Michigan College of Engineering 1st Year PhD Fellowship!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Start</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_006/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_006/</guid>
      <description>I joined the Real-Time Computing Lab at the University of Michigan as a PhD student!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduated with B.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_005/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_005/</guid>
      <description>🎓 I graduated with a B.S. in Computer Sciences at UW - Madison!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face-Off Paper Accepted</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_004/</guid>
      <description>Our paper, Face-Off: Adversarial Face Obfuscation , got accepted at PoPETS 2021!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interned at Roblox</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_003/</guid>
      <description>I started my software engineering internship at Roblox Corporation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First paper written</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_002/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_002/</guid>
      <description>I finished my first paper, Rearchitecting Classification Frameworks For Increased Robustness !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Start</title>
      <link>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_001/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bjaytang.com/en/news/post_001/</guid>
      <description>I joined the Wisconsin Privacy and Security Group at the University of Wisconsin - Madison as an undergraduate student!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
